(Howard:)If I may abruptly change the subject,
did you and Penny finally...? You know.
(Scene:)-Howard.
-I don't care...
(Howard:)...but my genitals wanted me to ask.
(Leonard:)Tell your genitals what I do with Penny
is none of their business.
(Howard(to his genitals):)He says they didn't do it.
(Leonard(to Sheldon, entering):)Sheldon, over here.
[CHOKING]
(Howard:)What are you doing?
Well, I feel bad for the guy.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, why are you sitting
by yourself?
(Sheldon:)Because I am without friends.
(Sheldon:)Like the proverbial cheese,
I stand alone.
(Sheldon:)Even while seated.
(Leonard:)Come on. We said we were sorry.
(Sheldon:)It's going to take more
than an "I'm sorry"...
...and an apology pie from Penny
to make up for what you've done to me.
(Kripke(arriving):)Hey, Cooper.
Read your retraction e-mail.